Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/amirhadzic (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Web Development
Web Design
Graphic Design

Languages

Croatian (Full Professional) Serbian (Full Professional) Bosnian (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Microsoft Certified IT Professional (MCITP)

Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer (MCSD)

Amir Hadžić

YouTuber With 330.000+ Followers. Professional Web Developer. Influencer of The Year 2017.

Summary

First Bosnian YouTube Creator with 280.000+ subscribers on my channel, and 50+ million views.

Professional Web Developer since 2009. I work with modern web technologies to achieve simple but powerful solutions. Microsoft Certified IT Professional and Solutions Developer (MCITP & MCSD).

Experience

YouTube Entertainer March 2010 - Present Bosnia and Herzegovina

Entertainment

Amilma Digital
Founder & CEO
May 2009 - October 2016 (7 years 6 months)

DASTO semtel

Network Administrator May 2011 - September 2011 (5 months)

Internet provider support and management. Brand development, web site traffic growth, web site UI and advertising revenue. Developed brand strategy and statistics systems.

Education

Microsoft

Microsoft Certified IT Professional & Solutions Developer, Information Technology · (2011 - 2011)